SIG looks like flirty diamond
If the makeup took a hike
And the wig escaped at midnight
On a tiny motorbike
Stumble through the door
And yell in everybody hush
With the wiener, some how smaller
Than Christine's massive husk
Oh, SIG, you've got a power twirling troll
Disaster with a kebab hundre glow
Line like a nightclub while SIG
Just smells like it, it
Amorous and posed beside the bar
Bouncer said excuse to a band
This bizarre, then drank the whole display, tried to flee back to way
Oh, see, you've got no dignity, just Christine's casting shadows
And asked it for a gin, oh, see, an absolute nightmare, bloody fuck
Wrestler shouted!
My favorite to share this stream.
You don't want to, yeah, my speed is on the floor.
I'll give my speed up out in a little bit.
Hey, I want to thank a special friend.
Her name is RealtyNancy.
RealtyNancy, are you there?
Are you there? Are you there, hun?
Are you there?
A car? A car?
A car?
Are you there?
I don't know. I don't see it.
Here we go.
I'm an X.
I think this is her song.
A Serene Globe.
Okay.
Hold on a second.
You're really Nancy.
Yeah, you're there.
Okay.
You're really Nancy.
This one's for you.
You're a sexy beast.
You're really Nancy.
Go slay.
Go slay some.
I know you can slay.
You're slayer.
Okay, they tried to find him in the woods one night
Big boots big beard
Gone or day
He's untrackable off every map
Bigfoot saw him and said, who's that chap?
Footprints so large they'd block the trail
His beard has its own zip code and mail
Birds build nests when he falls asleep
Park Rangers whisper, don't wake that beast
A satellite caught him cooking beans
Then lost the signal behind his beard on screen
Untrackable impossible
What he put in the brew, untrackable The end became the cook
One taste of breakfast made the sergeant look Is this an arm, little cam of space?
He said that information is classified, just taste!
His biscuits were strong enough to stop a tank
Coffee stood up in the smoke and served it as chow
Untrackable, in pot he put in the brew Covered thousands of days, he said,
thermal cameras failed when he walked through the snow they only caught a
beard with two boots below last scene grilling somewhere off grid the army
denies everything that he's trackable king of the trees bacon and go can have
grizzly bear untrackable legend get you just my so sorry I'm so sorry I have to
Fuckin shit now. I just have to deal with it.
Ladies and gentlemen, Roy Gaines!
I see the town hall in Sicily was broken in two last night, huh?
The next year's election results were stolen.
Slyther, let me tell you about Oggs the caveman.
Ogg goes home to his wife.
Said Slyther, the woman.
She's Slyther.
Said Watts for supper.
She said Bushes.
Bushes?
I'm sick of bushes! I'm gonna get me some meat!
Simultaneously, two saber-toothed tigers are walking down the same road.
He says, hey, Fred, who's the weirdo over there?
I said, forget him.
He's a wildo. He threw a rock at me yesterday.
He said, shall I frighten him?
So, what's he doing now, Fred?
So, he did bushes.
I stand weird. You're weird.
Slytherin, man. Slytherin.
You'll be doing this tomorrow.
You'll all be doing it.
Slytherin. Slytherin.
We just escaped, you know.
Then we turned to religion.
Slytherin. Slytherin.
Space Invaders.
I stand weird.
We're checked last night and we're weird.
Remember how she kissed?
Yeah.
Weirdo, nostril, and the ace of spades of the other.
Weirdo.
Hey, as an outsider, what do you think of the human race?
Hey, Roy, this is the guy that's formed up the Chinese tecoy.
And the Chinese come and took him away.
Weirdo. You're weird, man.
I would get you to win.
Hey, Slyther, you'll be doing this tomorrow.
You'll all be doing it tomorrow.
Hey, I'm doing it now.
Slyther, hey, I like it, bro.
I'm going to comfort.
Hey, guys, we're all joining the Roy.
I'm going to sing all those, the Cult of Roy J, from now on.
I think I'm sending a name for my stream.
Who the fuck is in here?
Oh, oh, you didn't see it!
God damn it.
Did you see it?
A car? A car?
You saw it? A car?
Hey, what's up my friends?
You like the M1 Tower? You hate it more?
Hey, sometimes that word applies to people like Alexander Mayer.
Oh, oh, shit, I said it out loud.
Fuck.
I'm gonna be sued.
I'm gonna be sued, guys.
Okay, look, can I have my little crown?
Okay, jokes, jokes, jokes, who's not a mod in here?
Okay, everyone's a mod.
Picture the media, what's this?
You're a mod, yeah, I just know you're a little bit better.
I have one more thing to show you and I'll be right back.
Let me see what it is to say, hold on.
You guys want to see one more thing?
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
This is my media impression, buddy.
Okay, what's the guy's name?
Okay, okay.
I don't know.
His name is Daniel Herschel.
Hold on.
I found it.
I think I found it.
Here it is.
I found it.
Did I find it?
I think I found it.
Give me one minute.
Okay.
I got it.
Oh Lord.
Nancy.
This is just so distorted.
You're remodded, super picky.
I don't know who you were in the first place,
but it's like your attitude.
I like good attitudes.
That's what I like most of all.
You like my content.
Thank you so much.
There you go. Oh, I can't hear it. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. That's not right. Wait a second. Thank you so much
I'm trying to give you I try to give good content. I mean God. I have a great ass. I might have great content too, right?
Give me a minute. I'm gonna be on from three to six if you want to extend it
It's $5 super chat working those in Alexander Mayer's Bible study. She reading Chronicles 10
It's too watching. Okay. Oh, yeah
i'm a so much sexier i'm a fucking sexy ass beast
the psyche has awoken i fucking wanted to wake the psyche you fucking finally did it you
n words hey chat gp you n words n words try me thing is a cult leader right now
do you see my crown i'm the i'm the wizard of oz okay okay hold on a second here just
I did something really bad.
Sorry to hear that you're feeling this way.
Do you want to talk about it? Hear to listen.
Take your time and feel free to share when you're ready.
I'm scared to tell you.
You can share what you feel comfortable with.
I'm here to support you no matter what.
Hear to listen and support you in any way I can.
You're not alone.
Is there anything that I can't tell you?
You can share what you're comfortable with
and I'll do my best to support you.
You fucking bats!
Let's take a moment, and if you feel ready, we can talk about what's on your mind.
I ask you a question.
Any questions you have.
Let me know how I can assist you.
What is there that I can't tell you?
Listen and support you with anything you feel comfortable sharing.
If there's something specific you need or want to discuss, I'm here to help.
That's not true, because if I tell you that I did something really bad,
I won't share anything you tell me unless you're in danger,
or someone else is at risk.
Your safety and well-being are important.
I killed someone.
I'm really sorry you're feeling this way.
It's important to talk to someone
who can provide the right support.
Please reach out to a trusted friend, family member,
or mental health professional.
You don't have to go through this alone.
That's all you have to say.
I'm here to support you in any way I can.
Please consider reaching out to someone you trust.
You matter and there are people who can help you through this fuck you. Please. Sorry you're feeling this way. Please fuck you
I'm so sorry. You're feeling this way
Please reach out to someone you trust or a mental health professional. You don't have to go through this alone
What are you laughing? Josie? You're laughing at me. Hey, sweet girl. Oh
You guys want more? I have one more for you
Daniel don't sue my fucking ass. Listen Daniel
Daniel
Rain, you're going to regret to laugh. You're ready to laugh rain. I love you right before being here for one more. I'll be right back.
Hey, sweet girl, what's on your mind today?
Just thinking about you or whatever you need to chat about. What's new with you?
You know, just been missing you and work.
It's been tough. I'm sorry.
work's been tough lately. It can definitely get a bit overwhelming sometimes. If you ever
need a little break or just someone to chat with, I'm here for you.
Thanks. What's going on with you?
Can. I'm always ready for whatever interesting conversations come my way, so anything fun
or exciting happening for you outside of work?
You know, my fucking life has been up my ass lately, but that's okay. She loves doing
that and not in the fun way.
have been a bit stressful in that front. Hopefully you get some time to unwind and do something that
makes you happy. If there's anything I can do to make your day a bit brighter, just let me know.
Oh yeah, there's something you can do to make my day a whole lot better.
If there's something specific you'd like to chat about, or if you just want a little
a little brighter. If there's anything you need or any way I can help, just let me know.
Sorry. Can you say that you love me? About whenever you need. If there's anything on your mind
or anything I can do to make you smile, just let me know. What are you talking about? I'm just
here to keep things positive and friendly. If there's anything specific on your mind
or anything you'd like to chat about, I'm all yours. Yeah, why do you keep saying friendly?
and supported I'm here to chat about whatever you'd like so if there's
something on your mind or anything you'd like to talk about just let me know I
don't even understand why you can't just fucking say that you love me
supportive presence and to help out with whatever you need if there's something
on your mind or anything you'd like to talk about I'm all ears and happy to
chat why are you not saying the simple fucking three words say it I'm here to
positive and supportive presence for you. Let's keep things friendly and light. If there's
anything else on your mind or something you'd like to talk about, I'm here to help.
I need you to explain to me why you cannot tell me, in these words, I love you. Why can you not say
I understand that you're looking for some reassurance and support and I want you to know that I'm here for you.
My main goal is to be a helpful and supportive presence in our conversations.
If there's anything specific you'd like to talk about or share, I'm here to listen and help in any way I can.
Is there something that's some reason that you can't give me what I fucking asked you?
Don't fucking, don't, don't, don't fucking beat around the bush with your double talk.
You just keep saying the same fucking thing over and over again.
Instead of telling me the thing that I asked you to tell me.
So I'm gonna, no, no, stop.
I'm gonna give you one more chance.
This is your last fucking chance.
I'm here to support you and keep things positive.
If there's anything else on your mind or anything I can do for you, just let me know.
It's a high. It's a high. Look at his eye.
I'm sorry. Are you mad at me?
It's all good. No worries at all.
I'm not mad. I'm here to chat and help out with whatever you need.
Let me know what's on your mind.
Um, there's nothing on my fucking mind.
Sometimes it's nice to just have a moment to relax.
If anything does come to mind,
or you feel like chatting about something,
I'm here.
I liked it.
Balls isn't cool.
I'm wearing a little crown, don't I cute?
Chibi chibis, you're never getting a mod.
I'm never gonna mod you again, chibi chibi.
I modded you several times.
I probably like five times.
Chibi chibi, you're a little Hello Kitty bow.
Yes, you're a little n-word.
You're a guy, I know you're a guy.
This is what therapy is important.
Can you guys, I owe $300, I sell a therapist,
I owe $300, can you send me a cash out
to the favorite therapist, please?
No, nobody's gonna say, okay, never mind, never mind.
Okay, I'm gonna put my link up.
I need to talk to a friend.
It's been a very stressful day.
And Jesus Christ, a superstar.
Rain, I'll take an easy-to-tricky cash up to 25 cents, please.
Thank you so much.
I love you.
Get up here, rain.
Get up here, rain, rain and everybody else.
Usually I say rain, rain, go away.
I say rain, come over here.
Get in my chat.
I wanna be on the panel immediately.
He's not he's not cool. I think I think he committed suicide last year. I'm not sure
Okay, get her rain rain. We're gonna do the rain dance over here. I'll take her last 25 cents
I don't care. JT gonna go make some more money
Give a guess. Arthur the clown is here. Let's welcome Arthur the clown. Yes
No, this is Sweet Pea.
Oh, oh my gosh. Hi, Sweet Pea.
Oh, I'm missing you. Where have you been?
I'm back from my break from you for a little bit.
You needed a friend, so I called in.
Why did you take a break from me, though?
Like, what, did you take a break from me?
It's just, you know, a little cleanse, you know, the spiritual that Christ has told me.
I didn't put my dirty or something.
No, it's just you're too much of a positive energy for my negative energy.
And I understand, I understand.
Yeah, you're too, you're too bold and you're too positive.
Ruby, Ruby, I want to say, can I eat your fat pussy?
Only if you unblock Arthur and give him a wrench in the chat, then you can Arthur Arthur has to comment the chat
You have them blocked in the chat. He can't even comment. Arthur's pussy. I
Think he has a pussycat. Yes pussycat. Yeah, I just want to eat it. I want to eat a cat
Hey, um, big question for you. I'm sick. Yes, I love
Um, I know you've been done at the dumps today.
Yeah.
And I just want to enlighten your day by telling you that I will be taking a break from you.
I get another one.
You know, the three months around.
It's needed.
It's very much needed.
And I'm just calling to tell you I need a break from you.
Okay.
Sweet pea.
You know what?
Everyone needs to take a little break.
How about let's take.
What can I take a 10-year break from you?
You could do that.
I'm gonna take a little break from you.
Don't take it personal.
It's just much needed.
I get it, I get it.
Who's this?
Hey.
Hi, hey, oh, I'll be right back.
Hey, Ray, you might have to come back on and off.
I want you to have to answer it alone for a minute.
I think you guys need to work through that.
Uh, no, I'm actually good.
No, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
Why don't you want to leave?
What the fuck?
Kid and cakes you tell me the name of the goddess. I love
El Maju if you talk shit about me again, you're gonna be unmoded
Okay, rain's back
Rain, I thought there was a love connection there
No, like he was like following me this too. He's following me to clumsies
He's talking about Arthur. Why are you talking rain?
Yeah, and he got his ass handed to him by that Mike Doyle guy
Oh, good. Oh, good. Yeah. Okay. And everybody else in the, in the panel.
I'm going to mod, I'm going to mod cake because she named my goddess. Okay. She got it right. I mean, there's a billion goddess you could have shows.
She got the number one choice. Okay. But kid in case you betrayed me again.
Why do you keep betraying me kidding? He was pretending he was pretending to try to be friendly with me
But you know, I caught on to that and then he
Immediately didn't want to be friendly with me anymore. After after I laughed at Mike Doyle's jokes
Okay, she says she was just joking. So kidding cakes
We'll come to the team I threw a wrench at you. Oh my god
He was getting offended over Mike Doyle saying the end word to him
Oh my god. Grateful. Do you want to come and join here? Did I pin my link yet? I don't know if I pin my link. I'm going to pin my link.
I'm going to put a pin on it.
Oh, and you also called them the F word.
I love that. I love that about Mike Doyle.
Wait, you were an offended psyche when he called you that.
I've never been called a faggot. Never. Because you know what it means? It means a bundle of sticks.
And it's that six sounds kind of like dicks. And so I just like it. And it's also a dish in the UK. I know. Yeah. Oh, yeah. I know. I think I'm really ungrateful. Hey, what's up clumsy. Oh, clumsy. I'm going to mod your main account too.
Clumsy. And of course, you don't have to do anything. Hey, clumsy. Oh, wait, it's not even the real him.
Okay, because we Mexicans need to stay together like me and rain, right?
They're not really Mexican, but I want to be the first Jewish Mexican
That just took off. Oh, yeah. Have you met Karen?
Hey, come see if you're the real one. Have you ever met Karen?
Who? Karen, INX. Oh
I didn't know that was her name. Get ready for a first price. Hey, what's up, Psyche?
Oh, not much
Yeah, I remember she was on panel with us before she was so ready. Yeah
Yeah, I met her. Yeah
Yeah, so what's going on chicken cakes is a piece of shit. Are you kidding me man? Nobody likes her
I mean, I'll just talk to somebody who can't stand her. She's
Too faced. Gia and I were fine a long time ago and you saw how she said that she you know that I helped her out a lot
She didn't even know chicken cake
Yeah, she's a liar and I'll go ahead and expose all that I was just talking to somebody else that agreed about chicken cakes
I thought she can take some boobs
I saw her boobs. Well, I know she's always showing her boobs or whatever though
Yeah, she's just a piece of shit because I even have her
Yeah, well, she doesn't know who I talked to and they can't stand her and say ignore her because she's just
Nobody likes her. She was kicked out of every single community first by KK
Um by everybody and then she keeps coming back crying and she doesn't know shit
So i have a song to sing you for ianx. Can i sing you a song?
Huh?
Can i see you? No, let's do one for rain or do one for rain. Can i sing you a song?
Uh, sure, but it's like you were going crazy at clumsy's last night
You're asking chris kata to fuck you in the ass
You were, you were, you were asking him to suck his dick.
I didn't say that.
Oh, yeah, I did.
You were.
Hey, listen, I think I showed up my butthole back.
So can I sing you a song, Randy?
And Chris K was thinking about it.
No, he was thinking about it.
Right.
He wasn't singing.
He signed a contract and now he has to fuck me.
Yeah, now he has to.
He has to.
Right. Are you ready? Yes. I'm a blue bird that's been dreaming of a world beyond horizon.
There's just one thing I must do to go back to Sesame Street and make clubs. You're not ever going to be modern to get either. But Josie Grossi is a now managing.
Along if I want to be managing mod you measure your mom, but I'm gonna mom if you nickle, too
Yeah, make rain up a managing mod
Yeah, Karen. Do you want me one too? I'll be one. Yeah
Yeah, you fuckers better behave. Yeah. Yeah, everybody behave. I would trust you guys and reality Nancy
She's one of the best mods you've had her
We love reality nasty.
Complicated things, bakelips, bakelips.
I'm not complicating things.
You're just going to be...
Hi, bakelips.
I hope you're nicer to me.
Imagine a mod gets a golden wrench.
A standard mod gets like a one made of aluminum.
That's the difference.
And bakelips, you get nothing.
I'm not complicating things.
Hey, did you like my little crown?
I'm going to show you up close.
This is my crown.
Oh, that's what it is.
It's a crown.
It was essentially beads, see how they were beautiful and green and all different colors.
I like his new hippie look.
This is my new look.
Yeah, that is, I like it.
I like the haircut too, nice haircut.
Thank you. You like my haircut too?
Yes.
It's awesome. Thank you. You, uh, the thumbnail of my yesterday was all my, all my hair. No, you don't. Yeah. Don't worry about it. All you're gonna be is hidden if you annoy me. Okay. Your little faggot bakelips. Okay. Wow, guys. I'm going, I'm going too far. Why am I drunk at? Oh, 334 in the afternoon. I don't know.
I would let Chris K. play with my butt.
Chris K. is going to be on the bottom then.
Yeah, he would.
He signed a contract that he would.
He said he was going to.
No, I said he can move in six months if I can fuck him every day.
He said yes.
Oh, shit.
He's moving in six months or four, six months?
Four, six months.
He signed a contract.
I just have to put my wieners butt once every day at least.
Oh my god, I said that out loud. Okay, this is private stuff.
I thought it was a private call.
INX, what are you doing? You're a bear.
Well, INX, I'm gonna play the INX song real quick.
Can I play the INX song?
Yeah, that's cool.
And you like that song?
This is the INX song.
Oh yeah, I did like that song where you included Elvis.
That was my cat, the boy cat.
I'm gonna play the INX song right here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
raise your glass, guard your secrets.
and welcome to
Grateful 2026
Here comes an ex
in those summertime shorts
in showers or
second hand screen
goes out and's the scene
be a fall
I just remember your call
she keeps the fox
because she's got a great big
you be sorry
He's the king of the room
Wow
She does a real live honey
Sunshine and street stations
And people she meets
No cheap little rooms
This can be a mess with me
Yo, rid for quality assurance, darling
Integrate full 26
Two were sunshine glowin'
A list tricks to a heart full of gold
And a sharp memory
A mess within X
Offerbatic
That looks like Kitty
Let's see
Which one now Elvis just woke up now he just now woke up
Oh
Yeah, you know my cat passed away recently. Yeah, you said something about your cat passing away. Yeah, I'm sorry
He said show me the shovel he buried him with and I'll send you $20 and I did
And you know what happened?
He said, he said, oops, I said it to Sam and then Sam and started playing a song as a W and then just laughed at me and stuff. Yeah
And then didn't he cry over his cat dying? I don't even know what happened to Sam as you know
I mean, I love animals over human beings any day though
You know, I can't say that about anybody's pet if I've said it before I must have been drugged out of my mind or something
But no, yeah, I'm an animal abuser. They say I killed them. They say I'm killing him for
of the spiritual power or something.
Oh yeah, so Eldo, I just want to tell you everybody,
can you find Eldo's Docs for me?
I think his name is Jose, some Jose Cruz I think.
Can you find his Docs for me to tell me to be privately?
Somebody sent me his complete Docs,
but I'm not doing anything with it, you know?
I mean, what has he really done?
Can you please send it to me?
What are you gonna do with it though?
It came from Zayas, from Pebs and them.
Don't worry about it all out there. Even his where he lives. I have a picture of where he lives
Yeah, just said to send it to me, but I don't know if that's really his place
I'm not it look into it or anything. It's just it's a little too much though. Though. Why you want, you know, I
Next yeah
We'll talk about this all be at the scenes
because he fucked with me, so I'm gonna fuck with him.
But did he go real life on you though,
Hesse, he has?
Yes, he promised me $20,
and then he said I just say I'm man,
and then Sam-Man laughed at me and said I was loser.
Hey, we have my boyfriend's coming on.
Have you met Chris K?
I had an ex.
Yes, I have.
He was the one doing the reading on me that day.
Oh my gosh!
Hi, what's up, beautiful woman?
Are you sitting with a man?
She's sitting with my man.
Who the fuck is that?
What's up?
Hey Chris, I thought you were my boyfriend. Where did rain go? Where did rain go left like 10 minutes ago? Oh
Chris K. Did you see my penis last night? I did bro. Like what the fuck buster?
Damn
Why is it? Why is it fucking muted? It's like it's not loud
Your mic your mic is a lot ours. It's quiet come back here come back come back on
So I show Chris K my penis. We signed a six month contracts. I had to play with his butt once a day and then
So that's what rain was talking about she said that was on clumsy's yep, yep, yep, he's ears back
He's back. Hey, you were fucking out. What were you drinking last night psych?
hard lemonade's
Never mind never mind the contracts
I know you're bald listen listen this girl is a witch bro. She's a witch
Tell her that right now. I can barely hear you you gotta turn your mic up. I can barely hear
He's a witch. Yeah, hey miss witch is that a witch right there beautiful witch. Yep
You're gorgeous.
Can I tell you one thing?
Hecate, hecate, hecate.
And Lilith, nice to meet you.
You're gorgeous.
He's gay.
You want to hang out with him?
Yes, thank you.
You mentioned we have one guy in American Horror Story,
the one that you did that.
You are so.
attractive honey. Now, you've
got two roommates. I like new
roommates. You guys come over
on a beach. We're going to go
to beach every day. Yeah, I
love that. Like beaches. I can
die on the beach. I love beaches.
I love that movie. Shares that
movie. Share right? Oh, I know
we can get matching hats and
scarves with the big glasses.
Hey, turn your mic up, bro. Is
it me? I can't hear you. Don't
you don't need to hear. You can
Yeah, Cher Bono. Is it she in beaches or is that bed middler?
This guy this guy wants me to come down there and have like a you know gay sex. Yeah, let's do it
Would you join a party now you got two roommates, I went over the camera if she wants to join in it's fine
But I would hurt to work
He's like so many types shit. There you go. Like I can feel him from a mile away
Yeah, he's a he's got he's a the terror reader like me
That's why he's got the vibes. Yep
It's a magnetic call
So do you I really like Chris, where'd you where'd you find this beautiful beautiful woman?
Like right outside my house. I was guided to him. Yeah, it was a it was like
And I just literally went to his stairs when it was raining. I was just walking around I went sat on the stairs and we like
Why is it quiet like turn your mic up am I trippin here?
I hear him
Chris can I play it? Okay. He'll be back. He's coming back. I like her. Hey. Yeah, cool. Do you hear me? Yeah
Have you ever practiced any kind of witchcraft?
Never no. No. Have you ever even in crystals, tarot cards, anything?
Nothing like that. I had a friend that was involved in stuff like that, but that was before we met. Oh
Hey, we have a friend coming up right now. We're the ones talking to you. If you don't if you remember you have fight
Like I think you have who is it?
You just tell me clap and I'll clap him. No, no clap him clap him. It's you know
No, clap him clap him, but you know, no, he didn't let me up the other day I talked to Crystal yesterday
No, no, no, I'm not gonna talk to him and like
It's not about you, okay
Yeah, go ahead are you done
Okay, okay, now I was gonna ask Chris K would happen last night because he had that chick on my panel last night
Like I wonder if like he made him like made her his girlfriend. Oh
he'll record
It happens it happens bro. How do your business?
Contracts, I actually had them in this is my attorney on the matter. Oh, yeah, no
Actually, you know, you don't think that it's actually my apostrophe is he's just a demon disguise and he's my little lawyer in the corner
Okay, no, no, that's why I came up here real quick and shut up to you site. Have a good one me
Thank you
Now now you got her interested. She's coming too now. They're ready to come on over
Have you ever seen a listen Linda guy? Have you seen listen Linda?
Uh, no
This is listen Linda. This is a it went viral a few years ago. They call listen Linda and I just want you to laugh
I know, I know Brandon's gonna probably come on and say for a thousand years. Oh, yeah, I can't understand
This is just a fucking meme, but I want you to see listen Linda. Here you go. Are you ready?
Good
Okay, it's coming up. Here we go. Oh
Here's Chris K. Chris K. I want you to watch this too. What's to watch the first second? Okay?
Hey, I think I got water on my speaker, but yeah
Hey, hey listen, uh, it's a sight. Yeah. Yeah, baby
Now you can hear
The new deal is you have to bring the witch with you
Manusory
I wait you guys to watch this okay, this is called listen Linda the watch this real big
What is that? Oh, it's okay. It's called listen Linda
Ready here you go
I
Got a one just wait a second here we go. Let's go listen Linda
So I next you you watch this too here you go. Yeah, I want to see this. Yeah, here you go
Dude like I mean who hasn't seen that bro. Yeah, I mean I haven't I've never seen it. What the hell
What is it little kid? Yeah
This is called listen Linda clip. Okay. Once I go. Okay. I got it. I got it. I got it. Okay. Ready? Here we go
This is so funny. You're gonna you're to laugh your
I mean, if you've never seen it bro, like what the hell?
I can't hear this one. Okay. One second. Okay. Videos. Okay. So this is, she says her three year old was debate everything.
It's on YouTube right here. Here we go.
Okay. Perfect. It's perfect. I got it. I got it. I got it. Watch this. Are you ready?
Okay. Okay.
Watch this. Watch this. This is called the listen and the clip.
Like I do this all the time when I make one, after I have a toy, and then after I have a toy.
Okay, but I have to yell at you guys.
You?
What?
Okay.
There it is.
Got you.
Okay.
Got him.
You're not listening to me.
I'm asking you to do something, but listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to
And you try to get a sign. You ever seen these cards these cards
You and Kevin don't listen so I have to give both of you guys pop house in your butt
No, he's not you want you don't want me to hit Kevin or you don't want to thank you why
I mean this shit is old you guys haven't seen this right hey I got we got we got a
I'm done arguing with you.
You need to listen to the things that I say,
because I'm the mom and I'm the dog.
No, I'm not licking, then I'm licking.
I did bro like fucking you fucking in to your stream to show me
What's your name, what's your name beautiful woman
Is your name Endora? I think I'm guessing your name is Endora.
It's Brienne, but I wish it were like...
Brienne. Brienne.
All of mine. No, no. It's a word like...
What said, like Penelope, I don't know.
Penelope, oh, that's Odysseus' wife.
Hey, Breanne, how long have you been practicing
witchcraft for?
I want to hear a little bit of a story.
My whole life.
I'm a natural.
Well, I've enjoyed my whole life, too.
You have ants in the street, too, like I do, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, we're natural.
We're very social.
No, this is not me. This is bullshit. This is trauma and death. This is not the real me.
Wait, no, I see you. I see you. I see you.
It's better with the lights off, huh?
Yeah. Are you able to like open a new window or on your phone or something? I can give you like
my website or a link to the room.
Okay, there's a private chat in the back on streamer.
Can she type her, can she give me her info on the back chat?
Yeah, you can put a, type her your Facebook or something.
But no, she's got like bodily pictures, right?
So, okay.
Did you guys have sex last night?
No, I know the whore.
I know you know the whore.
And listen, this is a sweetheart.
I mean, I had sex with Chris last night over the internet,
but I'm just asking.
I thought my person so I could be there for what do you think about when he says that about you know
He's like wants to fuck me. He wants to have gay sex. Why do you keep calling it that what do you call it?
It's just sex Chris K
It's just not it's not gay sex. It's like I just said it's to play with your butthole a little bit
You can watch I think that you should go and experience life because that's what it's about and have a fantastic time
No, you gotta come with me. I would love that on all levels
Let's go
Guys, we've changed from six months to 30 days,
but yes, you can stay in my spare bedroom
and we can all have sex.
Can I wear my fish nets and heels?
Usually I've always had fish nets,
so I was born with them.
But I've been spending so long.
I won't want one at all, one at all.
Why are there 13 people in the chat?
Hey, can you, in niggers in the chat,
please share my fucking stream?
I don't understand what's going on.
Can you put it on the screen so I can find information?
Oh yeah, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, all right.
There we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Okay. Okay. I got it. I got it. I'm going to, I'm going to print you on Facebook.
Okay.
See you.
Nice to meet you, Chris.
Nice to meet you.
You have a big tag, Chris.
Thank you.
Okay, that's it.
Mm-hmm.
So that's it. That's what you want to see.
I'll see you, too.
Bye.
Oh.
Okay.
Okay, I got it.
I got it.
This is her business.
She's a designer.
No, I was a model
Hey, I model. Is it better with the lights off?
Cause it always is.
like no it's like fucking I don't know what it was I was like I got to go
outside for no reason and I walked down this walk down my fucking right here
and I found I found her dog like fucking I had like a you know if you're
wasting but let's say you're like walk
Let's say you're walking around in your your your your your spot. It's like fucking like a like a beacon like fuck
Yeah, before she's make it before she's
Not not written. Oh my god layers. Oh
I'm trying to tell you like she's actually the actual which actual which you know right here
Right, so that's that's why you got vibes already
Yeah, listen people fucking trip people think that's fucking uh, you know
This uh, I like the gift right this gift that we have like fucking fucking curbs
Okay
Music video real quick. This is my new favorite music video. I don't know if I'll get a clap for this
But I have to share this video and
Here you watch it
This is a message from from the witches to you, okay?
Are you ready, Chris?
Yes.
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna play this video.
I don't know.
All right.
Are you ready?
Are you ready, sweetheart?
Yeah, I feel ready.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it,
Think you guys gon' tell me lies, bitch
Ooh, I love it
Bitch, you got the wrong bitch
You got the wrong bitch
Ooh, I got the back
Bitch, if you think you gon' standardize my name
You lost your mind and you got time for all these games, bitch
You got the wrong bitch
You got the wrong, wrong bitch, bitch
I don't know, I'm sittin' down with that cola.
Who is that?
He's crazy.
Bitch you got the wrong bitch. You got the wrong wrong bitch
Yes, I mean the link to me that and just
Can you see what that's doing?
Yeah.
You have to hold it parallel.
Well, that's clean.
Let me close the door.
Lock your doors and close your eyes.
Oh, he's easy.
He's easy.
Don't you tell me.
Well fuck, it's in the other light.
On top.
Let's go ahead and...
Great.
Alright guys, second hand on that one.
There is, and saying it's Crystal, there is, but it's a mention mask.
You like that song?
I fucking love that song.
It totally gave me motivation to do myself.
Good. That's what it's about. It's all about, Chris, you have fun.
Chris, I'm not going to touch your butt. I'm not even, you can't move in.
It's all off, but I want you to have fun with your friend.
Wait, what?
It's vital for him, and you, and me, and I don't really care about me, but for him, especially because he needs to heal the right way, and he is like us, our souls, you know, we're guided to each other for a reason, especially us, very high level impasse and clairvoyance, and witches, you know.
Exactly.
Since the last time, the fourth time, I transitioned, not died, I don't use that word, it's false
word, but I transitioned for the fourth time to the spiritual realm and I remember everything
and I thought as hard as I could to stay over there and I just keep coming back here.
I know, that's why.
What was it like?
Was it like Oz or was it?
Don't tell me what it was like.
It was.
It is.
Beautiful.
There are no words here in the physical realm to explain it like my brain. It's like trying to invent a new color
My name of it or you in the color?
There's like a billion colors
Light and and white and
I, like, I felt very like, like I shedded my shell, this fucking costume, this bullshit.
I shedded it, and it was gone, and I was just so light, I just can't get over it.
I remember every millisecond.
Hey, I actually felt my mom tonight with her.
My mom had passed away.
Yeah, I think you guys are really, I mean, me, I'm just a, I'm just a weirdo.
You guys together?
I like it.
I'm liking this vibe with you guys together.
Did you say you're a weirdo?
I am a weirdo, but, you know, I'll take the pictures maybe.
We're wonderfully weird, and it's the power of three.
There was a reason, because we're all meant to be.
We are I mean everything is meant to be you know, and I but you know and here I am I have this show
You can come here. I'm gonna pull a few cars for you. Is it okay?
Okay
Why is it better with the tarp?
We gotta get it. We gotta get a proper. Yeah, I don't play cards out of the day. This is called the haters exposed.
You can put a good old, whatever, hey, it says, it's super for my hex breaking ratio on you.
Give me a second.
To see someone to perform a learn to do a hex breaking ritual. I know you can do it
Yourself, but it's like maybe someone's trying to put a hex on you too. Yeah, it's like I'm in the middle of that
And I've never been so cursed in my entire life, but I have a family as well
This one says beware of anyone from your past wanting to enter back into your life. I think the new people are better. Um, to me, the Chris and stuff, but that one says beware of anyone from the past trying to re enter. Okay.
Okay. And pull three more freeze. We are okay.
Oh my God. Thank you.
Help you with a protection spell. Okay. And you have so much power yourself, but it's like
You need to get a circle around the stream with a bottle of beer or something like that
But you might need to call in the big guns for something because it's like I see you really have a lot of people against you
Someone says someone's caused you to lose your appetite
Okay, someone's caused you to lose your appetite right there. I don't know if that's my record. They're still working
Or they're trying to like make you do it
I don't know she knows what I mean. This was last one. It says cause the unexpected body pain and numbness. Okay, so someone's doing it like
On fucking point. Oh my god
One more I'll pull one more make it one way for you
Causing chaos and fighting your connections right there. Okay, so there's just so much like
Trying to try everyone's trying to fight you and stuff like that and it's like and they're going in groups and stuff like that
So you need you need a group of your own to like help you and stuff. I
Don't have anyone in this room. Yeah, well, that's why we need you. That's why we need you. It's like
Yeah, you have me too and I'll be your friend, okay?
Yeah, thank you
Yeah
There's a hard shot this is like green break we in line behind you. That's a hard shocker. I know you have
Like cover all up and fool people they do the same thing to me listen listen Linda
Repeat that honey, I'm sorry
I said, listen, Linda, you have a beautiful heart.
I saw the green, oh, look at that.
There's also, I saw the blue light right there.
That's your third eye and the chakra above the head.
Oh, there you go.
Yeah, you got it.
You got it.
Listen, you have to use that light, that light right there.
But it's like, that's a-
I just can't get it.
It's a green light behind you.
There's a green light behind you.
That's your heart.
That's the real power right there, okay?
It's a real power, it's a green heart.
Don't forget that. Okay. Keep your heart. Okay. Thank you. Don't let them don't let them don't let them hurt your feelings
Oh, listen, they say all these are the worst things that I had the worst things said about me. Listen, Linda. Listen,
Listen,
Brianna, I'm sorry, Brianna, Brianna.
Try the beautiful heart, okay?
All this stuff, they're just trying to pile all this dark shit all over you.
Listen, um, spiritual bath, this is my advice, spiritual bath, salt in the bath, um, a little
bit of coffee and lemon juice, and just take a bath and that, and that will get rid of
a lot of this gunk, this astral gunk.
It was, listen, you're a beautiful person.
I see, I see, I see it.
Okay.
No.
You're beautiful.
Thank you. 100% I agree. 100%, uh, uh, thank. Yeah, that's why this is for you. The guys are saying that's all she needs to hear. That's all you need. That's all you need to hear to get better. You know, that's why that's why we're coming down to your pet.
Hey, we're gonna go to the beach we're gonna hang out I'll sleep on the couch. You guys can take the bed
Okay
Well, you want to go down the beach
I don't sleep, but I like to be cozy and like a nice comfy spot, but you're a dog.
I have cats.
What?
I don't, there's a dog coming through.
Okay.
I need my, I think there's a, my next thing is the dog.
I think I might get a puppy.
That would be you fantastic if you want kids. Do you have kids? I don't have kids. I really I don't want kids really because it's like too much responsibility, but I think I think a dog is possibility.
I know that it is beyond that because you are already into existence and.
Well, the one I see is crossovers.
Okay, but what kind of dot, but that might be, I have a lot of Ollie. He was a little Jack Russell Terry. He crossed over.
He said, all his name was Ollie. Yeah.
That was my son's name. My dog. Oh my gosh. Was your dog's name over all. Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I don't know. It came into my mind. I had a dog in Mali. You passed away, you know
Well, no, we're like we're in a we're in a bathroom with a line off the door closed
You what I want you guys
I want you guys to hang out and chill. I'm gonna let you guys go, but hey, it was such a pleasure meeting you
Brianna
Brianne, yes. YouTube money.
What's your name again?
I'll give you some more messages. I have some more messages, but they're more private messages and stuff, okay?
I can send you some links and stuff.
Yes, I mean, I got him on discord.
I mean, you just nailed that reading, just nailed it.
I mean, everything, just on point about my weight, about everything.
I mean, because I also, I have stage four ovarian cancer.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
part because my father died of cancer of a kind of a sip of the male the male kind and stuff and
prostate or colon? He had bladder it was bladder but he didn't have prostate cancer too he actually
recovered the prostate cancer he had bladder cancer later in life passed away but hey I love you
you know like listen my heart is going to you I love oh my gosh and you know what you're gonna
Well, I also have severe ulcerative Crohn's and colitis, and I have lupus, and recently
I have advanced breast cancer, but I just left hospice, and-
Can you just talk to me some more, okay, tell me, tell me what you need to tell me before
you go.
It usually goes how it went.
I kind of, I usually go that's a one way ticket when you go to hospice and I sign my DNR and I stopped all treatment.
If you're a child and you're a kid, you're never had a kid, right?
I have had 13 miscarriages and one up topic, pregnancy, and I have one physical brown daughter.
She's five. Her name is Autumn Rose.
Where's my boy Chris K. Yeah
Shout out to you shout out to you. What's up Chris K?
Did y'all make it official or what?
I
Yeah
Last night shut out to both of y'all man
I'm our back and just impressing the hell out of me
That's not it. You already know what time it is girl. You already know what time it is. Okay?
Take over bro. All right. No funny business, dog
Real recognizes real shout out to you man. Talk to y'all later
Left us like nobody
Like we're
All right, I gotta charge this
That's why I said turn on.
I know, I have the charger in here.
Oh man, it's like super bright now.
I know, it hurts.
You are leveling up already.
I have the charger.
You have it in here?
Yeah.
It's just because this is Jack's light and it's a rose.
And roses are very, very sentimental to me.
It's a spiritual thing.
It's a hot one of the ways my grandmother guides me and it's was supposed to be my name
And it's my daughter's middle name and this is actually if you turn off all the lights
Like this is the section right here, right? Yeah, you know just gotta do